>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在我的论点是，我总是从人民中回来，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now the argument
I always get back from people,
而你们中的一些人也许正在想
and some of you may be thinking
this at this moment is, yeah,
但即使我坐在你的工作室里我也学会了这些细微差别
but even if I sat through your workshop
and I learned all these nuances and
我读了那个规范我的代码库上的那些小恶魔呢
I read the spec, what about all
the junior devs on my code base?
他们永远不会懂这些东西
They would never understand this stuff.
事实上，在理论上，我几乎比任何一个问题都能找到我。
This I actually, in theory, hits me
almost more than any question I ever get.
这种心态说我够聪明的
This mindset that says,
well I'm smart enough but
那些小鬼子太蠢了
those junior devs they're too
dumb to understand this stuff.
这完全是无稽之谈。
That is complete and total nonsense.
我不知道你的背景
I don't know what your backgrounds are,
but
你们每个人都很出色
everyone of you is
excellent at what you do.
您可能知道 JavaScript 的更多或更少，但这不会使您变得更笨，
You may know more or less about JavaScript
but that doesn't make you dumber and
不太了解事物的能力，学习事物的能力更少。
less capable of understanding stuff,
less capable of learning things.
我不相信我们应该这样做
I do not subscribe to
the belief that we should
把我们的密码基础降到最低的共同标准
dumb down our code basis to
the lowest common denominator.
您应该尽可能有效地使用这些工具。
You should absolutely use the tools
as effectively as you can.
您应该尽可能了解如何使用这些工具。
You should be as obvious about how
you're using the tools as possible.
当有人在代码库中谁不理解
And when somebody is on the code
base who doesn't understand,
把它作为一个学习的机会。
use it as an opportunity for
them to learn.
使用代码复审，
Use code reviews,
使用对等学习的文化，配对在一起。
use a culture of peer-to-peer learning,
of pairing together.
所有这些都有助于每个人更好地了解工具的运作方式。
All of those things to help everybody
learn how the tool works better.
当你收到密码审查的时候，一些初级的开发者做了一些蠢事，
When you receive a code review and
some junior developer did something dumb,
就好像他们没做任何胁迫一样也许有个角落
like they didn't do a coercion correct and
maybe there's some corner case they didn't
知道吗，你不拒绝密码评论，说，你是哑巴。
know about, you don't reject the code
review and say, you're dumb.
你说嘿过来跟我坐一会儿
You say, hey,
come sit with me for a minute,
让我跟你谈谈你不知道的那个街角的情况
let me just talk to you about this corner
case that you weren't aware of, and
如果你做了这件事我们会彻底避免角落里的
if you did this thing instead we'd
avoid that corner case entirely.
现在你学到了更好，学到了更好。
Now you learned better and
they learned better.
这是一个完整的掩体论点这是一个懒惰的借口
This is a complete bunk argument,
it's a lazy excuse for
不想在我们的开发团队中做我们应该做的事
not wanting to actually do what we ought
to do on our developer teams, which is
大家应该学习，每个人都要向上。
promote that everybody should be learning,
everybody should be headed upward.
我不在乎你在哪里，我在乎你的方向是什么，你要向上吗 ?
I don't care where you are, I care what
your direction is, are you headed upward?
您是否了解有关工具的更多信息 ?
Are you learning more about your tool?
这不是不使用工具的借口。
This is not an excuse for
not using the tools well.
这也不是聪明的借口，对。
It is also not an excuse for
being clever, right.
有人说，这里的斜坡问题是很危险的。
Some people say,
well the slippery slope argument here.
我可以做这些聪明的数学运算，对。
I can do all this clever bit-wise math,
right.
我在用这个工具我很聪明
I'm using the tool and
I'm being clever, and I'm doing all of
我在一个代码行上编程，我们以前用 Perl 做的方式。
my programming on one line of code,
the way we used to do in Perl.
我也不是这么说的
That's not what I'm saying, either.
我想说的是你的密码是一种通讯方式
What I'm actually saying is that your
code is a form of communication, and
有一种有效的通信方式，能够很好地理解和使用该工具。
there is an effective way to communicate
that understands and uses the tool well.
如果您请求代码的读者了解有关工具的信息，请
If you ask the reader of a code to
understand something about the tool so
他们可以理解这条代码，那就是对他们的投资。
that they can understand that line of
code, that is an investment on their part.
确保投资超出该行代码的范围。
Make sure that that investment
pays off beyond that line of code.
确保当他们了解如何工作时，他们会看到更多的信息。
Make sure that when they learn how that
worked, they're gonna see more of that.
他们知道你是怎么做怪事的
Rather than,
they learn how you did something weird,
然后他们就再也不用再利用这个了
esoteric bitwise trick, and then they
never get to use that ever again.
那是浪费他们的时间
That's a waste of their time.
让你感觉好但那是浪费时间
Makes you feel good but
it's a waste of the time.
这也是为什么我们有如此多的努力才能有良好的发展文化
And it's part of the reason why we
struggle so much to have good dev culture,
我们没有把重点放在促进所有人都能理解的问题上
cuz we're not focused on promoting that
everybody should be able to understand.
从三个星期的人到其中一个人
From the person who is three weeks into
JavaScript to somebody who's been at it
像我这样的二十年
for 20 plus years like me,
我们应该能够在同一个代码库中进行互操作并进行良好的沟通。
we all oughta be able to interoperate on
the same code base and communicate well.
是啊小鬼子需要学习一些东西但那就是
Yeah, the junior devs gonna need to learn
some stuff, but that's what happens in
每个行业每个行业都要学习一些东西
every job and in every industry,
you have to learn some stuff.
你没看到建筑师说
You don't see an architect saying,
我们不打算把这栋大楼设计得太好了
well we're not gonna design that building
well cuz we've got an intern on the job.
你教实习生如何构建好建筑
You teach the intern how
to build the building well.
这就是我们要做的
That's what we need to be doing.
我们需要使用 JavaScript 的所有部分，但是
We need to be doing with all
parts of JavaScript, but
尤其是每个人都能让你忽略的部分
especially the parts that everybody
tells you to ignore like types.